A Guide to the Near East Foundation records Accessions 2009.104, 2010.002, 2010.020 FA406
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2009.104: Near East Foundation records, 1915-2003; 1940-1980; AC 2009:104; 180 Cubic Feet 168 boxes, including 150 standard record storage boxes
  - USAID Task Orders and Reports
    - End of tour Repts. - Tanzania TO9 - Gail A. Bagley, Joe Schmid, W.B. Decklemann, L.J. Fabricius, 1968-1970 (Box 2)
    - End of Tour Report T.O.9 - W.B.Decklemann - Tanzania - Opga, 1968 (Box 2)
    - End of Tour Report - Dr. John L. Hilstrom - Tanzania - Veterinary/Research Officer T.O. 9, 1968 (Box 3)
    - End of Tour - Wm. B. Decklemann - Tanzania T.O.9, 1970 November (Box 3)
    - End of Tour Report - Tanzania T.O.9 Mr. Duane A. EWriksmoen - Irrigation Officer T.O.9, 1970 November (Box 3)
    - End of Tour Report - Tanzania T.O.9 - Dr. William W. Peek, 1969 (Box 3)
    - Completion of Tour Report - Tanzania - T.O. 9 - W. Joe Schmid - OPEX, 1968 (Box 3)
    - End of Tour Report - Tanzania T.O.9 - Mr. Even C. Thompson, Irrigation Agronomist, 1968-1970 (Box 3)
    - End of Tour Report - Tanzania - E.G. Van Voorthuizen - T.O.9, 1971 (Box 3)
    - End of Tour Report - Tanzania T.O.9 - Evert G. Van Voorthuizen - Pasture Research Officer, 1967-1969 (Box 3)
    - End of Tour Report - Tanzania - Theodore Yee - T.O.9, 1971 (Box 3)
    - End of Tour Report - Clark, Dr. Andrew A. - T.O.9, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Van Voorthuizen, E.G. - T.O. 20 - Range Management, Pasture Improvement, 1971 (Box 3)
    - End of Tour Report - Tanzania T.O.9 - Theodore W. Yee, 1967 May 31 - 1969 May 30 (Box 3)
    - Task Order No. 10 - Togo - PIO/T 693-004-3-66666407 Amendment 1, 1966-1969 (Box 3)
    - Togo, 1965-1966 (Box 3)
    - End of Tour Report - T.O.10 - Togo, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
    - End of Tour - Togo - T.O. 10 - David L. Olson - Vocational Ag. Advisor - Team Leader, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
    - End of Tour Report - Togo - T.O. 10 - John H. Mullenax - Vocational Agricultural Advisor, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
    - Task Order No. 10 - Togo - David Olson, 1966-1969 (Box 3)
    - End of Tour Report T.O. 10 - Lorell Sorensen, 1966-1968 (Box 3)
    - C-193 T.O. 10 - End of Tour Reports Mullenax & Olson, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
    - C-193 T.O. 10 - Tour End - Togo - Sorensen, Olson, 1966-1968 (Box 3)
    - Task Order No. 11 - Kenya, 1966-1973 (Box 3)
    - Reports - T.O. 11, 1968-1972 (Box 3)
    - Work Plan - T.O. 11 - Kenya Reports, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Annual Reports *First T)-11 Kenya, 1968 April (Box 3)
    - Annual Report *Second TO-11 Kenya NEF Report on Contract, 1969 April (Box 3)
    - Extra Annual Reports - Kenya - TO-11, 1968 April - 1969 October (Box 3)
    - Annual Reports *Third TO-11 Kenya NEF Report on Contract, 1970 April (Box 3)
    - Annual Report *Fourth TO-11 Kenya NEF Report on Contract, 1971 April (Box 3)
    - Annual Report *Fifth TO-11 Kenya NEF Report to AID/W - Contracts Office, 1972 May (Box 3)
    - Annual Report Range Management Division *Kenya, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
    - Reports - Helphenstine, Russell - TO11 - End of Tour, Annual, Quarterly Work Plan Range Mgmt Ad., Rift Va. Pr., 1969-1971 (Box 3)
    - Annual Report - TO11 Dr. Wayne M. Durdle, Range Management Adv., 1971 April - 1972 April (Box 3)
    - Reports - Durdle, Dr. Wayne M. TO11 Range Mangement Advisser - Kenya, Site Reports, Quarterly, Annual, 1970-1972 (Box 3)
    - Task Order No.11 - End of Tour Report, Dr. Wayne Durdle, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Kenya - Wayne M. Durdle, Site Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
    - Reports - TO11 - Kenya - Voelkel, Traveis T., Range Management Ad., work Plan, Quart. Coast Province, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
    - Termination Reports - Travis T. Voelkel - Kenya, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Reports - TO11 - Kenya - Voelkel, Travis T. - Quarterly and Annual, 1972 (Box 4)
    - Monthly Reports - Voelkel - Site Reports - Kenya, 1969-1972 (Box 4)
    - Africa - Travis Voelkel, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
    - Reports - TO11 - Kenya - Luebbe, donald J. - Extension Coord., Training and Misc., 1971-1972 (Box 4)
    - Luebbe, Donald J. - Reports Annual Report, 1971 May - 1972 May (Box 4)
    - End of Tour Report - TO11 - Kenya - Donald J. Luebbe, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
    - Task Order NO11 - Donald J. Luebbe - Work Plan and Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 4)
    - Kenya - Donald J. Luebbe, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
    - Monthly Reports - White, 1967-1969 (Box 4)
    - Africa - Ulverd U. Alexander - TO11 Kenya, 1969-1970 (Box 4)
    - Reports - Alexander, Ulverd U. - TO11 - rural Development Adviser - Kisumu, K., Work Plan, Quarterly, Annual, Final, 1969-1971 (Box 4)
    - Task Order NO.11 - Kenya - End of Tour Report - Elgin M. Cornett, 1971 (Box 4)
    - Kenya - Work Plan - Elgin M. Cornett, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
    - Africa - Cornett - TO.11 Kenya, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Monthly Reports - Cornett, 1967-1969 (Box 4)
    - Work Plan and Reports - TO11 - Cornett, Elgin M. RD Adviser, 1969-1971 (Box 4)
    - Reports - Moon, Floyd. D. TO11 - Special Reports - Memos kenya, 1967-1970 (Box 4)
    - Montly Reports - Moon - Site Reports - Memos Kenya, 1967-1970 (Box 4)
    - End of Tour Report TO11 - Moon, Flyod D. - R.D. Adviser Coast Province, 1967 January 15 - 1969 January 15 (Box 4)
    - Reports - Moon, Flyod D. TO 11 Kenya - Annual Reports - End of Tour Report, 1969 March 3 - 1970 December 17 (Box 4)
    - Africa - Moon TO11 Kenya, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Kenya - Work Plan - Floyd D. Moon, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
    - Africa - Goodloe TO11 Kenya, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Kenya - Work Plan - Sid Goodloe, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
    - Report - Goodloe, Sid - TO11 - Kenya - End of Tour - Range Management Ad., 1967 January 5 - 1969 April 10 (Box 4)
    - End of Tour Report - TO11 - Kenya - White, Larry D., Range Management Ad., 1967 October 20 - 1969 October 19 (Box 4)
    - Kenya 0 Mr. Larry D. White, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
    - Monthly Reports - Slade & Schleicher, 1967-1969 (Box 4)
    - End of Tour Report - Kenya TO11 - Ervin W. Schleicher, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
    - Kenya - russell R. Helphenstine, 1969-1971 (Box 4)
    - Africa - Finance TO11 - Kenya, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Africa - Orrice - General Correspondence TO11 - Kenya, 1967-1971 (Box 4)
    - Africa - Personnel Allow. Finance & Leaves TO11 Kenya, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Africa - Personnel - Travel TO11 Kenya, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Africa - Purchase, Shipping & Supplies - TO11 - Kenya, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Africa - Slade - TO11 - Kenya, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Africa - Annual Progress Reports TO11 - Kenya, 1969 (Box 4)
    - Africa - Quarterly Reports - TO11 - Kenya, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Colorado - Reports TO11, 1966-1968 (Box 4A)
    - Task Order No. 15 - Dahomey, 1967-1969 (Box 4A)
    - Task Order No. 16 - Niger, 1967-1969 (Box 4A)
    - Budget Information and Worksheets - Morocco - Task Order No. 17, 1968-1975 (Box 4A)
    - Mr. Herbert D. Floyd - Reports - Morocco TO17, 1970-1971 (Box 4A)
    - Harper, Louis W. - Reports - Morocco TO17, 1971-1973 (Box 4A)
    - Mr. Arlan B. McSwain - Reports - Morocco - TO17, 1971-1973 (Box 4A)
    - Mr. Clyde C. Searl - Reports - Morocco TO17, 1971-1973 (Box 4A)
    - Reports - TO17 - Morocco, 1973-1979 (Box 4A)
    - Reports TO17 Reports - General, 1974 (Box 4A)
    - Reports TO17 Sanford M. Anderson, 1973 June - 1974 January (Box 4A)
    - Reports TO17 Reports General, 1972-1973 (Box 5)
    - Task Order NO17 Morocco Reports, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Reports Morocco TO17, 1970 (Box 5)
    - C-193 TO17 Qtrly Rpts Morocco 1st-14th, 1968 December - 1972 March (Box 5)
    - C-193 TO18 Ghana Annual Reports (2), 1970 July, 1971 July (Box 5)
    - TO18, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Task Order No. 18 - Ghana Annual Report - First, July 1970 (Box 5)
    - Task Order No. 18 - Ghana Annual Report - Second, 1971 July (Box 5)
    - Task Order No. 18 - Ghana Annual Report - Third, 1972 July (Box 5)
    - Task Order No. 18 Reports - Fourth Annual Report, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Task Order No. 18 Reports - Fifth Annual Report, 1974 August (Box 5)
    - End of Tour Report - Duane E. Loewenstein - Task Order No. 18 - Ghana, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Reports - TO18 End of Tour Report - Dr. Duane E. Loewenstein, 1971 (Box 5)
    - End of Tour Report - Robert E. Adcock - Task Order No. 18 - Ghana, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Task Order No. 18 - Ghana - Reports - Misc., 1970-1971 (Box 5)
    - End of Tour Report - Fred E. Winch III - Task Order No. 18 - Ghana, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence - TO18 Genearl, 1971-1973 (Box 5)
    - TO18 - Ghana - Annual Reports, 1971 July (Box 5)
    - Dr. Duane E. Loewenstein, 1969-1974 (Box 5)
    - Reports TO18 - End of Tour Reports - Dr. Henry Hopp, 1971 (Box 5)
    - TO20, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Reports - TO 20 Tanzania - Hansen, Wesley J. - End of Tour, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Task Order No. 20 - Reports - Moris, Donald L. - Water Resources Dev. Spec., 1971-1972 (Box 5)
    - End of Tour Report - TO20 - Don Moris - Water Resources engineer Masai Project, 1972-1974 (Box 5)
    - Reports: TO No.20 - End of Tour Report: James T. O'Rourke, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
    - Wm. W. Peek: End of Tour Report, 1972 February 15 (Box 5)
    - Task Order #20, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
    - End of Tour Report - Warren C. Putman, Livestock Prod. Off.- Task Order No. 20 Tanzania, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Reports: T.O.20 - Warren T. Putman, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Talamai (Kijungu) - Ranching Association Management Plan, 1974 (Box 5)
      - Untitled Blueprint, 2016:FA406:001; 1.2 Cubic Feet (Folder SF1)
    - Work Plan for Masai Team - Task Order No. 20, 1974 (Box 5)
    - T.O. 21 - Budget Revised, 1974 (Box 5)
    - T.O. 21 - Agricultural - Materials and Services Project - Paper (Prop) Rev No 1, 1969 (Box 5)
    - TO 21 Reports: Elijah, H.D., 1973 (Box 5)
    - End of Tour Report - H.D. Elijah TO21, 1975 March (Box 5)
    - Report - Engle, John C. TO21 - End of Tour Report - Teacher of Coop Accounting - Tanzania, 1971-1973 (Box 5)
    - Reports: TO21 - Gaarder, Raymond O., Lvst, Mktg. Splst. - End of Tour Report, 1973 (Box 5)
    - TO21 - Reports: Dr. Raymond O. Gaarder, 1972 (Box 5)
    - TO21 Will R. Getz - Reports, 1950-1972 (Box 5)
    - End of Tour Report - TO21 - Mr. Kenneth W. Stokes - Agricultural Economist, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Report - Stokes, K.W. TO#21 - Tanzania - End of Tour Report - Agricultural Economist, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Report: Nutritional Approach to the Planning of Food Production in Tanzania by Levon Yeganiantz, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Watson, Dr. Barrie D. TO21 - End of Tour Report - Tanzania, 1973 (Box 5)
    - C-193 T.O.22 Gen. Corres. - See Termination of Order & Personnel, 1971-1973 (Box 5)
    - C-193 - T.O.22 Terminaiton of Order & Personnel - Uganda, 1971-1973 (Box 5)
    - C-193 T.O.22 - Uganda - Tour End Rpt. - (Wood, Thompson - locate Merinar), 1972-1973 (Box 5)
    - Reports - Task Order No. 23 - Scotty Deffendol - Chad - Cameroon - Quarterly Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
    - Task Order No. 23 - TDY Report - Reports - Scotty effendol - Chad - Cameroon Area, 1971-1973 (Box 5A)
      - Untitled Blueprint, 2016:FA406:002; 1.2 Cubic Feet (Folder SF2)
    - Mr. Scotty Deffendol T.O.23 - Livestock Specialist - Chad, 1970-1974 (Box 5A)
    - AID/aft C-193, 1971-1976 (Box 5A)
    - Shipping Personal Effects - Scotty Deffendol - Cameroon TO23, 1974-1975 (Box 5A)
    - T.O.23 - Chad, 1974-1975 (Box 5A)
    - Task Order Reports TO23 - Miscellaneous Reports - Chad-Cameroon, 1972 (Box 5A)
    - Report - TDY Scotty Deffendol - Chad-Cameroon Area - Task Order No. 23, 1971 November 29-December 22 (Box 5A)
    - Deffendol Mfg. List, 1974 (Box 5A)
    - Purchase Order No. 7152 C-78 - Scotty Deffendol - Purchase of Truck - Rec. - Parts from IHC, 1974 January 2 & 10 (Box 5A)
    - C-193 D.O. #23 Deffendol Final Report, 1976 (Box 5A)
    - T.O. 23 (Box 5A)
    - Task Order No. 24 End of Tour Report - Thomas E. Hamilton, 1974-1976 (Box 5A)
    - End of Tour Report - Helseth, Thos. P. - Lesotho - TO25, 1973 January 22 - 1975 April 21 (Box 5A)
    - Inspection Report: J.E.J., 1971-1973 (Box 5A)
    - Inspection (Young) Report - "indway" / Mor. Leb. Gr. Jor. Ir., 1972-1973 (Box 5A)
    - Recruitment Trips - James E. Johnson, 1971-1973 (Box 5A)
    - 1971 Trip Reports, 1965-1970 (Box 5A)
    - "Contract" AID/Afr 193 - Washington DC Reports Index, 1964-1974 (Box 5A)
    - C.J. Spalding - Trip Reports, 1969 (Box 5A)
    - T.O.1 Reports Quarterly, 1964-1971 (Box 5A)
    - Inspection Report - Dooley, 1971-1973 (Box 6)
    - Recruitment Trips: Dooley, 1971-1973 (Box 6)
    - USAID/Washington 'visits' - Dooley, Johnson, Wallin, 1971-1973 (Box 6)
    - Africa Trip - Mr. Johnson, 1974 (Box 6)
    - J. Johnson Trip Reports - Africa, 1974 (Box 6)
    - Trip Report - Inspection and Review - Africa - March - J.E. Johnson, 1974 March (Box 6)
    - Trip Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 6)
    - Young Travel Report, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Dr. Ketcham's Article for the Community Development Journal, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Report - Cattle Dips - Masai project - E.G. Van Voorthuizen, 1971 July (Box 6)
    - Report - E.G. Van Voorthuizen - An Ecological Survey of Masailand, Tanzania, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Oil Palm Project Ghana - Dr. Hopp and Loewenstein, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Cattle Project TO18 Ghana - Dr. Hopp & Loewenstein, 1971 (Box 6)
    - J.W. Taylor's TDY Report on the Agony Center / Dahomey, 1969 January-March (Box 6)
    - Experiments in Vegetables Growing - Carlier S. Rep., 1967 (Box 6)
    - Vegetable Report - Carlier extras, 1967 (Box 6)
    - Planting A Forest in Niger - F.R. Weber, 1966 (Box 6)
    - Herbert Floyd - Morocco - TDY Assignment, 1968 November-December (Box 6)
    - Forestry Notes - Weber, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Dr. Chas. H. Rust's Reports W. Cameroon - Potential for Swine Production & Poultry Marketing Potential, 1967 (Box 6)
    - Reports - Task Order 1 Quarterly, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Reports - Task Order No. 1 - Quarterly Reports, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Local Housing in Dahomey - J.W.Taylor S. Report, 1967 (Box 6)
    - Herbert D. Floyd TDY/Libya - Wheat Trials, 1969 March (Box 6)
    - Plan of Work & Calendar of Work from Gabriel C. Meaux, Dahomey, 1965 (Box 6)
    - J.F.M. Carlier / Niger Correspondence, Work Plan & Veg. Marketing TDY, 1969 (Box 6)
    - Goodloe-Payne Report on Range Management in Kenya. From Kenya Weekly News, 1968 October (Box 6)
    - A Guide to Well Consruction Niger - Leon O. Selle, 1968 (Box 6)
    - Dooley Travel Report, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Rice Project Report Ghana - Dr. Hopp and Leowenstein, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Report - Jordan - Boys Club Activities, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Report - F. Winch- Employment Generation in Agriculture, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Report - E.J. Sholton - Fiber - Long Veg. Fiber Industry, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Quarterly Progress report - Upper Volta, 1965-1971 (Box 6)
    - W. Cameroon - Dr. Wayne Robinson - Veg. & Other Food Crops Survey, 1967 January (Box 7)
    - Exportation De Legumes (Niger/UNCC) - French version by M. Glorieax (not NEF) Acccount of Trip to Europe by Glorieax & Carlier on veg. mktg., 1969 June (Box 7)
    - Peanut Oil Report - John Pankey - Togo, 1967 (Box 7)
    - Warren Putman - Livestock Survey - Niger/W.Africa - For Rockefeller Foundation, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Livestock Survey West Africa - Rockefeller Fdn./Warren Putman, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Maradi Young Farmer's Training (Niger) by Richard G. Koegel, 1967 (Box 7)
    - Report - Brunner, Dr. Henry A. - Proposal for Teacher - Education in Agriculture for Iran, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Report - Meeting of Voluntary Agencies Working in Africa, 1970 October 28 (Box 7)
    - Report - Livestock Development in Kenya, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Africa Contract - Legal File # I33 - T.O. #16 Niger - Personnel, 1969 (Box 85)
    - Africa Contract - Legal File #I33 - T.O. #16 Niger - Quarterly Reports, 1969 (Box 85)
    - Africa Contract - Legal File # I33 - T.O. #16 Niger- Surety Bonds (Box 85)
    - Africa Contract - Legal File # I33 - T.O. #16 Niger - Finance (Box 85)
    - Africa Contract - Legal File # I33 - T.O. #16 Niger - Contract (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File #I33 - Task Order #10 (Togo) - Contract, 1964-1971 (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File #133 - Task Order #10 (Togo) - Amendments (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File #133 - Task Order #10 (Togo) - Finance (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File #133 - Task Order #10 (Togo) - Personnel (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File #133 - Task Order #10 (Togo) - Purchasing, shipments & supplies (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File #133 - Task Order #10 (Togo) - Quarterly Progress Report (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File #133 - Task Order #10 (Togo) - Surety Bonds (Box 85)
    - Africa Contract - Legal File # 133 - T.O.#15 Dahomey - Amendments, 1968-1971 (Box 85)
    - Africa Contract - Legal File # 133 - T.O.#15 Dahomey - Contract (Box 85)
    - Africa Contract - Legal File # 133 - T.O.#15 Dahomey - Finance (Box 85)
    - Africa Contract - Legal File # 133 - T.O.#15 Dahomey - Personnel (Box 85)
    - Africa Contract - Legal File # 133 - T.O.#15 Dahomey - Purchasing, Shipping, Supplies (Box 85)
    - Africa Contract - Legal File # 133 - T.O.#15 Dahomey - Quarterly Report (Box 85)
    - Africa Contract - Legal File # 133 - T.O.#15 Dahomey - Surety Bonds (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File #133 - Task Order #4 (Niger) - Contract, 1968-1972 (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File #133 - Task Order #4 (Niger) - Education (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File #133 - Task Order #4 (Niger) - Finance (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File #133 - Task Order #4 (Niger) - Personnel (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File #133 - Task Order #4 (Niger) - Purchasing, shipments & supplies (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File #133 - Task Order #4 (Niger) - Quarterly Progress Report & Others (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File #133 - Task Order #4 (Niger) - Surety Bonds (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File #133 - Task Order #4 (Niger) - Amendments (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File # 133 - Task Order #12 (Dahomey) - Quarterly Reports, 1967-1972 (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File # 133 - Task Order #12 (Dahomey) - Personnel (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File # 133 - Task Order #12 (Dahomey) - Amendments (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File # 133 - Task Order #12 (Dahomey) - Contracts (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File # 133 - Task Order #12 (Dahomey) - Finance (Box 85)
    - African Contract - Legal File # 133 - Task Order #12 (Dahomey) - Surety Bonds (Box 85)
    - Personal - Duane A. Eriksmoen, 1968 (Box 106)
    - Erickson, Kenneth A. (Marilyn, also) Financial Analyst - ADB (Box 106)
    - Contract - Ericksson, Sigurd (Box 106)
    - Ericksson, Sigurd - Iran (Box 106)
    - Africa Quarterly Progress Reports (Task Order #4) Niger (Box 111)
    - Niger - Seed Analysis - Rutgers University (Box 111)
    - Africa - Quarterly Report - TO.#4 Niger, 1969-1970 (Box 111)
    - Africa - Weber, Fred - Task Order #4 Niger, 1965 (Box 111)
    - Africa - Agricultural Extension project - T.O. #6 Cameroon, 1964 (Box 111)
    - "Life in Cameroon" by Linda Williams (Box 111)
    - Africa - Literature - T.O.#6 Cameroon (Box 111)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Cameroon T.O. #6, 1969 (Box 111)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Cameroon T.O. #6, 1968 (Box 111)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Cameroon T.O. #6, 1966 (Box 111)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Cameroon T.O. #6, 1967 (Box 111)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Cameroon T.O. #6, 1965 (Box 111)
    - Africa - Office T.O.#6 Cameroon - Gen. Corresp. (Box 111)
    - Africa - Program of Work ( Task Order # 6) - Cameroon (Box 111)
    - Africa - Interim Progress Report by W.C. Putman - Upper Volta T.O.#8 (Box 111)
    - Africa - Literature - T.O.#8 Upper Volta, 1965 (Box 111)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Upper Volta T.O. # 8, 1969 (Box 111)
    - Upper Volta - Monthly Reports, 1970 (Box 111)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Upper Volta T.O.#8, 1968 (Box 111)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - T.O.#8 Upper Volta, 1964 (Box 111)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - T.O. #8 Upper Volta, 1965 (Box 112)
    - Plan of Work by W. C. Putman T.O.#8 Upper Volta (Box 106)
    - Africa - Quarterly Report - T.O.#8 Upper Volta, 1969 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Quarterly Reports - T.O. #8 Upper Volta, 1965-1968 (Box 112)
      - Untitled Blueprint, 2016:FA406:034 (Folder SF34)
    - Africa - Water Resources Project - T.O.#8 Upper Volta, 1965 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Trip to Bobo-Dioulasso by Warren C. Putman - T.O. #8 Upper Volta, 1965 August (Box 112)
    - Africa - Van Voorthuizen, E.G. - T.O.#8 Upper Volta, 1965 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Office - General T.O. #9 Tanzania (Box 112)
    - Central Establishment - Tanzania (Box 112)
    - Government - A.I.D. General (Box 112)
    - Africa - Calendar of Work T.O. #2 Dahomey, 1965 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Dahomey T.O.#2, 1969 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Montly Reports - Dahomey T.O.#2, 1968 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports T.O.#2 Dahomey, 1967 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports T.O.#2 Dahomey, 1966 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - T.O.#2 Dahomey, 1964-1966 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Personnel - Allow., Finances & Leaves T.O.#2 Dahomey (Box 112)
    - Africa - Office (Task Order #2) Misc. - Dahomey, 1965 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Personnel - Travel T.O.#2 Dahomey (Box 112)
    - Pilot Village Project Agreement - Dahomey (Box 112)
    - Pilot Village Project - Dahomey - Correspondence about Cement (Box 112)
    - Africa - Plan of Work T.O.#2 Dahomey, 1965 March 1 - December 31 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Program of Work T.O.#2 Dahomey, 1965-1967 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Quarterly Report - T.O.#2 Dahomey, 1969 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Quarterly Progress Report T.O.#2 Dahomey (Box 112)
    - Revised Extension Program - Dahomey, 1966 (Box 112)
    - Work Plan by H.A. Andrews - Dahomey, 1966-1968 (Box 112)
    - Dahomey - Work Plan 'Mr. Pieschl' (Box 112)
    - Africa - J.W. Taylor - Dahomey - TDY (Box 112)
    - Africa - Amendment - T.O.#4 Niger, 1965 (Box 112)
    - Niger - TDY - J.F.M. Carlier (Box 112)
    - Africa - Cars - T.O.#4 Niger, 1965 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Drawings - T.O.#4 Niger, 1966 (Box 112)
    - Niger - J.F.M. Carlier - Misc. (Box 112)
    - Niger - Monthly Reports, 1970 (Box 112)
    - Niger - Monthly Reports - Putman (Box 112)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Niger T.O.#4, 1969 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Niger #4, 1968 (Box 112)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - Niger #4, 1967 (Box 113)
      - Photos, 2016:FA406:035 (Folder SF35)
    - Africa - Monthly Reports - T.O.#4 Niger, 1964-1966 (Box 113)
    - Africa - Office - Misc. T.O.#4 Niger, 1965 (Box 113)
    - Africa - Projects - T.O.#4 Niger, 1964 (Box 113)
    - Land Rover Niger (Box 113)
    - Niger - Putman's Reports - Misc. (Box 113)
    - A.I.D. - Ghana (Box 113)
    - A.I.D. - Morocco (Box 113)
    - Government - African contract - A.I.D. - Tanzania Opex Contract, 1965-1970 (Box 113)
    - A.I.D.- Tanzania (Box 113)
    - A.I.D. - Uganda (Box 113)
    - A.I.D. - Washington, D.C. (Box 113)
    - A.I.D. - Kenya (Box 113)
    - Africa - Agreement (copies) - Original in legal file #133, 1964 (Box 113)
    - Africa - Beery's Field Trip Report - Niger, 1965 October 31 - November 8 (Box 113)
    - Africa - Final Reports A-K, 1966-1969 (Box 113)
    - Final Reports M-Z (Box 113)
    - Africa - Quarterly Progress Report T.O.#5 Malagasy, 1965-1968 (Box 114)
    - Robert Dunn - End of Tour Report, 1964-1966 (Box 114)
    - "Tafa sy Dinika", 1966 March 13 (Box 114)
    - Niger - A Guide to Well Construction in Niger by Leon Selle, 1969 (Box 114)
    - Niger - Community Development Extension Program for Niger (Box 114)
    - Planting A Forest in Niger by Weber (Box 114)
    - Africa - Guide for Extension Workers by Leon Clayton - T.O. #6 Cameroon, 1966 (Box 114)
    - Africa - Swine & Vegetable Production & Marketing Survey - T.O.#6 Cameroon (Box 114)